残酷な天使のように 少年よ 神話になれ
青い風が今 胸のドアを叩いても 私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
そっと触れるもの 求めることに夢中で
運命さえまだ知らない 痛いけな瞳
だけどいつか気づくでしょう その背中には
遥か未来 目指すための羽があること
残酷な天使の転生 窓辺からやがて到達
ほとばしる熱いパックスで 思い出を裏切るなら
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
XunG-15 hypothetically 恐れだけできたら
さてごきげる 予率がスパイシング・スパイシング・ China
its way over here I never thought I'd actually get a chance to fly on one of
these hot mamas man it's great having a famous buddy like you right Shinji yeah
I thought you must be getting sick of being cramped up in the mountains so I
thought it'd be kind of nice to invite you guys to come along with me on this
little day what are you saying that this is really a day we're having Masato and
I bought this cap especially for today just for you I'll never take it off so
where are we going oh we're just taking a cruise on that cute little boat down
there
oh my god one two three four five aircraft carriers and four battleships what a
flight that's your cute little boat she's gorgeous that's the pride of the UN
combined fleet the super carrier over the rainbow it's enormous personally I'm
surprised such a crusty old relic and still float yeah it's not so bad it's a
vintage model from just before the second impact damn give me a break it looks
like they've brought the power cables for that children's toy of theirs give me a
break
cool cool cool cool cool cool totally awesome this is way too cool I'm so happy I want to cry look at
there's antennas and dishes and guns and large pads oh man cool look at that oh look at those over there hey wait up get my hat stop
stop damn you that's my special hat stop it someone come on stop it
well hello Misato how have you been just fine goodness you've grown some
haven't you uh-huh and I'm not just taller my figure spilled out as well let me
introduce you this is a designated pilot of Eva unit 2 the second child Oscar
Langley saw you
what did you do that
that's the viewing fee quite a bargain niche it's overpriced but that's all right
here's your change
oh which one is the famous third child oh nine don't worry Oscar it's him not much to
look at hmm nerve and from your antics on the dick I was quite sure you were the
leader of this boy scout troop obviously I was mistaken thank you for all your
gracious hospitality oh no thank you for giving me the opportunity to babysit so
many more children and thank you for your assistance in the marine transport of
Eva unit 2 here are the specifications for the emergency power supply hmm you've
wasted a trip I'd never approve any request to activate that toy while it's
here in the first place think of it as being prepared for an emergency the Eva is
quite valuable sir so valuable that the entire Pacific fleet has to be pulled for
guard duty exactly when did the UN recommission us into a bloody cargo service if my
memory serves me correctly it was just after a certain organization was
established guarding a toy what a ridiculously grandiose assignment for the
entire Pacific fleet it's still not enough not when you consider the
importance of the Eva sign these transfer documents please not yet
Eva unit 2 and its pilot have been entrusted to us by the third branch in
Germany you're just not gonna waltz in and do as you please Captain cancer are
game will you transfer them to us once we've unloaded in New York a sucker the
ocean is our jurisdiction you will follow our orders here I understand however I should
remind you that in an emergency nerves military authority overrides your own she's awesome she
sounds just like Ritsuko well you're as confident as always mr. Kaji I must insist that you stop
inviting yourself under the bridge oh sorry about that please excuse us transport us to Yoko
as order damn those children of mankind salvation I suppose the times are
changing sir I understand that Congress has pinned its hopes on that robot as well
on that child's plaything what idiots if they've got the money to blow on that the
order gave us a little more
what are you doing here accompanying her I'm on a business trip of sorts talk about careless I
should have anticipated something like this so do you have a boyfriend right now I don't think that's
any of your business is it I'm hurt so I understand that you're living with Katsuragi yeah tell me
something is she still so wild in bed no she hasn't changed at all has she Shinji um I guess but how did
you know what my name was well I ought to know you you're pretty famous in the
defense business you know the famous third child who piloted an Eva in his
first battle with no training oh that I I was just lucky luck is a part of your
destiny it's your talent well I'll see you later okay it's a bad dream it's a nightmare
so what do you think about Shinji Ikari oh the great third child he's boring and yet his
synchronization ratio was well over 40 percent in combat with no prior training my god that
Admiral's attitude gets on my nerves he's full of himself all right too much pride's bound to make
him cynical that mr. Kaji is pretty um interesting he hasn't changed at all that chauvinistic pig hey
third child you're coming with me
that's really an interesting color I didn't know it was red that's not all that's different about unit
two unit zero and one were the prototype and test type respectively the fact that unit one synchronized
with an untrained pilot like you is proof of that however unit two is a little different my unit two is
the world's the world's first real evangelion created for actual combat conditions it's the final
production model what's that what's that it can't be angels angels you mean a real one
this is really bad we've got to go back and find misano
all ships pan out and take evasive actions radio room status report the silver lanes got silent
titus andronicus can't locate the target the box eblos is taken in water damn it all what the hell is going
on hello nerve delivery would you like to order data on this enemy and counter measures to use
against it this is our combat situation get the hell off my bridge this is just my opinion but I'd say
that must be an angel 80 field can't be penetrated with this kind of firepower but what is this angel doing
is it here is it after unit two
where are you taking me
just wait here a second
I don't believe this
why do all boys have to be such a bunch of perverted jerks
let's go oscar
why won't it sink only an eva can beat it
what
well put it on
don't stand there get moving
okay but what do we need these flight suits for oscar
are you dense we're going to defeat that angel with my unit too
no way does misano know about this
I'll get her permission after the fact
there get ready for an amazing display of piloting third child
just sit down and don't bug me
this is odd the angel seems to be looking for something
I wasn't expecting to see an angel this isn't how it's supposed to be
that's why unit two is there and I've generously provided a second pilot as a reserve
if worse comes to worst you can always escape by yourself
of course I can
it's a program error
it's thought noise
I told you not to disturb me
what do you mean
ah you're thinking in japanese aren't you if you must think do it in german
uh well I'll try strudel brotwurst
don't cough never mind we'll start over again switch language to japanese
evangelion unit two go
communication from the othello
ava unit two is activating
say what
all right oscar
abort stop the ava activation sequence
don't listen to that moron oscar go for it
what are you doing
that ava and its water out of my jurisdiction
you're violating my authority
you can't sit down about your procedures this is an emergency
oh dear lord unit two is still using the b type equipment
what if we fall into the ocean we're done for
then we won't do that
shenji are you in there too
yes ma'am hi
they're just kids
this is our chance
right
oscar take off
go
let's do it
where is it that way
we've got just 58 seconds left
i'm well aware of that
misato get the external power supply socket onto the flag deck
i'm on it
what's she doing now
right let's play hopscotch
hopscotch
the power supply is in place
reactor connection completed
all hands prepare for impact
this is nuts
ava unit two coming in for landing
oh what a waste
the target is approaching rapidly
angel approaching from nine o'clock
switching to external power
switch completed
we don't have any guns
the progressive knife ought to do it
it's gigantic
the bigger they are
what are they gonna do now
hand-to-hand combat is the best way to defeat the angels
looking good oscar
this isn't a game
look what you're doing on my flight deck
look it's sinking
it's impossible to fight underwater using the b-type equipment
well you know what they always say
you don't know until you try
how much cable is left
1,200 meters what are you gonna do
we'll deal with it
we've got to do something
the cable's about to run out get brace for the shock
the don't
ava has lost the target
i've got to change the disc
i've got to make a delivery so i'll just be taking off
well let's go
take care of the rest of this captain
there
he ran away
admiral the target is approaching ava again
here it comes again
right i'll finish it off this time
hey what's wrong it's not working
it's b-type equipment
what are you gonna do
what am i
you're the famous third child aren't you
do something
look
it's an angel
ava too has entered the target's body
does that mean that ava's been eaten
this is like morland fishing
fishing
that's it fishing
oh man it just goes from bad to worse
shut up you pessimist
and get off my lap you pervert
but we've got to free ourselves
aska do you read me
don't let that angel get away
huh
well admiral
what now
i'm going to need your cooperation
a point blank assault by the two surviving battleships
correct
we'll sink these two evacuated battleships in line with the umbilical cable as a trap
when the ava opens the angel's mouth both ships will rush into the opening
once inside the angel the ship's computers will be activated via remote control
they will then fire all of their bow turret cannons and self-destruct destroying the target
preposterous
preposterous perhaps but not completely impossible
i understand
all hands abandon ship
i repeat
what about the evangelion
don't worry about them
they'll be perfectly fine
hey don't
don't break mine
aim without my permission
shinji
asuka
do you understand the operation
i'll do the best job i can't
all ships open the kingston valve
scuttle at point z
reverse the cable
ava has started to surface
t-minus 70 to contact
hey are you rubbing against me on purpose
cut it out dork
will you quit complaining
we've got to open its mouth or we'll be fish food
t-minus 60 to contact
how's its mouth
it's still not open
both battleships are sinking towards the target
ava continues to surface
t-minus 50 to contact
it's stuck
there's no time left
target has passed beneath the tempest
do it
now don't get any strange ideas
like what
let's just concentrate on getting out of here
works for me
t-minus 20 to contact
t-minus 50 to contact
open open open open open open open
fire
my my my quite spectacular
i should have anticipated it but that was dumb
you're apologizing
are you okay
cut it out
at least we collected a lot of valuable data
i see
hmm
this data really is important
nice vineyard
they broke their synchronization ratio records
just for seven seconds
it must have been due to the danger
wait
hey
where's kaji
he took a powder
he's probably back at the headquarters by now that jerk
my goodness that was a rather eventful trip wasn't it
was it caused by this
i wonder
well it's already restored itself this far
it's frozen but it's still alive
quite amazing
this is the keystone of human instrumentality project isn't it
correct
this is the first human being
this is adam
she may have looked cute
but she was a real female dog
if you know what i mean
well at least we won't have to see her again
yeah but mr big shot here still gotta go work with her every day
i feel sorry for him
huh
i'm oscar langley so are you
charmed huh
fly me to the moon
and let me play
among the stars
let me see what spring
is like on jupita or mars
in other words
hold my hand
please be true
in other words
i love you
when a disastrous battle proves that asuka and shinji need to work on their ability to function as a team
misado comes up with a plan to make their dysfunctions functional drama ensues in the next exciting episode
and of course there'll be lots of fan service don't miss it
i love you